Wow
I don't know what just happened there. It looked like him. It looked like Hebrew Hammer
Oh my gosh, what else could go wrong? I mean that was absolutely shocking
I'm sorry guys, it's not been my day.
I think three out of three,
maybe like the third time's the charm or something like that.
Hopefully.
I mean, we're having these good groups
and then all of a sudden some dickhead has to come.
Bruh.
Oh, maybe sweet people call back.
I know.
That was a classic.
Classic.
Oh my gosh.
Jamie, Jamie just said I have a screen shot. Do I want the picture? I never want to see that again
That was disgusting that was terrible
I mean, I thought it's ah
I'm just in shock. Let me see. I'm gonna be shocked. I
Got fooled. I got bamboozled. I got bamboozled by the
Got the wiener
Everyone's right about me then. I'll get rid of the dick.
Okay, let everyone get in here.
Yo, Funky Time's toilet company. That wasn't you that did that was it? Oh, oh, hold on. Are you stalking Spunky?
Wow
I'm just a little speechless.
I'm wearing shorts, I look like I was.
Hey, okay, what's up?
What's up, what's up?
We just got home a good kid.
She's a coincidence.
Well, how is everybody?
I put the link up, I mean, link.
I mean, just having problems today.
I don't know, it's like, I think I'm going,
I need to pace myself, pace myself.
Okay.
Everyone's doing good, good and gracious.
Okay, that wasn't, that wasn't on Brandon.
Oh, it sounded like Hebrew Hammer, not Brandon.
I think someone started to frame Brandon, personally.
It sounded like Hebrew Hammer.
It sounded just like him.
Wrong.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know if I trust you.
I'm a lover, uno-lover.
In a ski mask, I think it was you.
It's not Brandon.
Stop trying to frame Brandon.
Now then, you're the weirdo.
Ooh.
You just know his voice by heart, yeah, sure.
Oh my god.
Said he rude hammer.
Yeah, there's a rude, oh yeah, you can see rude in here.
Tony said I'm not allowed to be live?
Oh no.
Not Tony. Oh, yeah. Oh, Tony, that gay guy?
Oh, yeah. I was just I was informed by my attorney not to listen to anything he said.
He's in love with me, though. He's in love.
The loser. Tony, Tony, Tony.
how's everyone doing? I guess I will premiere. I need to do something real quick so I want to
watch the premiere of this video here. I'll wait while everyone gets there and I'll premiere right
now. Enjoy the premiere of god mode, the initiation.
enjoy
It's better be correct
You thought growth would feel like light
It doesn't
It feels like pressure
Until you learn how to hold it
Not gold, not ease, it came unsteady
It pulled the truth up from below
Everything I didn't wanna know
Not who I was, but what I hid
All the things I never handled, never did
Every habit, every crack
Came forward, no turning back
This isn't power over anything
It's standing still while everything swings
And not collapsing
rise and change but change is fire without a name it burns the parts you thought were you
until what's left is something true this is god
Stay to open, every boundary left unspoken
Let the world just pull at me
Called it love, called it being free
But freedom without structure breaks
And openness as what it takes
To let the wrong hands map your mind
Until there's nothing left undefined
So I-
others could play so now I feel but I decide what leaves my mind what stays
inside not closed off just in control not every truth needs to be told
Deserves your time
Friction doesn't mean stop
It means something changed
I stopped explaining every move stop meeting everyone's approval started building before I speak let results replace the need
A number strained is not suppression. It's choosing timing not repression. You don't have
Can I speak Hebrew?
Uh, you know, a little bit of Yiddish.
Then I'm gonna just be ready a little, a little bit about to run.
Thank you, Nancy. Well, thank you for watching that.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I'm sorry. I know. I know.
I'm sorry. I've already had to see Tony's penis again.
Yeah, that was Gonzo from the Muppet show, actually.
It was, I think it was.
Yeah, that's that's what I said.
That's what I said.
I was like, I think it's Gonzo.
But unfortunately, but hello Urshina.
Oh my God.
I hope you like that. Actually, I really like that song. Oh, that was pretty good.
Hi, everybody. Yeah, so I guess I'm going to get my cards here. My labyrinth cards.
You need to do a muppet stream. I know, but that wasn't a muppet stream
That wasn't my idea of the muppet stream I wanted. Hey, what's up, Q? That was a you. That you Q
I don't know. Why are you saying wow?
Sorry
Wow, what that you I asked to see your penis, but not not like that. That was embarrassing
Sounded like
It's not like Hebrew Hammer.
Hugh, did you pour him on me?
You're in trouble.
I know.
I don't want to be.
It was a Muppet stream, but I didn't want that.
We really do. We want to do a Muppet stream,
but not that.
I didn't want the real Gonzo on my show.
I mean, those Ray-Bans,
how did those Ray-Bans fit on his wiener like that?
There was a very small bridge on the nose, you know?
No, you're used to, oh, okay, yeah.
So you have your old handle, okay, good.
Old black, at least, excuse me.
Q, why'd you N-word bomb me the other night?
I mean, it's like, trying to,
trying to, yeah, it wasn't the real gonzo.
I think I was an imposter.
That's why he was wearing those glasses.
Wow, okay, I'm gonna put my background in the back.
Everyone likes my background, huh?
There you go.
Here it is oh my god. I'm so sorry. Oh, okay there
Okay
I'm just that was oh my gosh. Oh, oh
Good morning
I'm loving your new music that you're putting out.
I like the male voices that you're choosing.
I like the, it's like it's a deeper level
of what you were doing before.
Thank you.
I like it.
Power song, the one, what is it called?
Laws of Power?
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Make more, if you want to, make more like that.
Yeah.
Because
It really does reprogram the mind a little bit.
I like that, you know.
Yeah, because there's so much music that is just like such like, you know, people listen to because people listen to music to be entertained and but it's actually like it's really easy for like negative messages to be put in music and so.
Um, you know, I'd like to put actually like useful, good things that can like, you know, help people in the music and, and I, you know, you're right, like I do listen to it and it is part of my.
reprogramming myself as well and well I like it I mean I I want to reprogram
myself to a certain extent just you know to survive in this world and you're
thinking is similar to mine and in a lot of regards but I really like
That kind of matador sort of theme Spanish-y Latin that you're going with lately. It's sexy
You know, it's funny. I was saying earlier this year
It might be a Latin boy summer and I think it's happening. I
Once did a white boy summer with my screens, but maybe this is this year. I'll be the Latin boys summer
I got to do something with that, but I love it. I love what you're doing. So I just came on to say hi and everything
What's new today?
Thank you. Yeah, I woke up. I'm just a little bit ago and
and
Looked like there's pretty good crowd on on YouTube out there. So but it's got porn bombs, too
Yeah, we thought it was gone really already. Yeah, it was on the last episode. It was like
We thought it was gonzo from the Muppets, but
No, I think it was an imposter because he was wearing glasses over his nose.
It was just, it was pretty shocking.
But yeah, it happens, it happens.
People are up to no good.
But I saw, there's a lot of, there's a lot of gossip going on right now.
Oh, there is still me and or
Well, do you care maybe you don't care? Oh, what's up? What is it?
There's a lot of vegan patriot gossip
Okay, right now
revolving around
This sidekick of hers known as Victoria J. Do you know about Victoria J?
I've she's been on the show and I did a reading for her before and
and you know
I know she's on IP2. I know that she, you know, she has a kind of funny voice and, you know,
those are mom and stuff, but yeah, I do see that she's kind of being talked about.
I think Kate had a picture of her as like a picture of a luau and I think Victoria J was the pig.
Yeah.
Do you think Victoria J is really a young woman or do you think it's somebody else or something else?
I am. I don't think that she's her picture. Her picture looks like, you know,
you know, Katie, Katie, let's not, let's see, what's Tom Cruise's ex,
Kate Holmes?
Yeah, he's like some kind of like cute, like,
and I can tell by the voice, maybe he's a different person, but
Yeah, yeah Victoria whoever Victoria J is is about to be exposed
So that's coming. Well, let me think what else
I
Didn't have anything to do with Q losing his channel
Somebody asked me about that and I didn't so I was actually disappointed to see that he lost his channel
even though I don't want to like talk to him or anything, but
Yeah, I think are y'all gonna stream together. How do we make this happen? That's what I'm trying to figure out because you're in the same state
You're you're not that far from from each other. I'd say
Maybe two hours or something. Uh-huh. Oh, I
Mean, I don't like
Does there need to be like a dono goal?
For more something like that to happen or what like we need like I guess transportation and like yeah
If he's down like
you know
he's welcome out here and
You go to the pier or something or I can go out there
I mean, I'm yeah, but I'd love to I'd love to meet him and I promise I'll you know keep my hands to myself
you know and we'll keep his hands to himself those two ways it's not like it's
but yeah so the main so the main hindrance is transportation and then there would have to be
activity money right yeah and uh because I I like I'd love to do IRL like um like a lot like um
And I met him right when I started my show too,
so I've known him for quite a while.
Brace him, and there will be no drugs, Kenneth, no GHB.
But yeah, I would definitely love to, you know.
Well, it would be better probably for him to come to your,
cause there's a lot to do in your area or so,
than where he is at.
Okay.
And yes, the Bakelips is saying hi, yes, loves you.
Bakelips.
Hi, Bakelips.
Yeah.
Are they in the chat?
Yeah, they're in the chat.
He's a, here we go.
And, yep.
He's wearing a beautiful wig, you see.
He's waving.
He's wearing a nice-
So.
I'm on almost a week with no cigarettes.
Oh, congratulations.
Good job, how's that going?
I don't feel like myself, honestly.
Like I'm happy with my choice with that,
but I'm not gonna say I'm never gonna go back to smoking.
I just am working on myself in a lot of ways.
Right now I have,
a few goals that I want to reach.
So I need to be more physically fit and healthy
and everything.
So, you know.
I got no big bit.
But it makes me, it makes me like grumpy.
Well, yeah, I think that is it.
It changed his personality totally.
Yeah.
When I think about it.
Yeah, yeah, I like him better.
with his new personality than with the other personality.
Yeah, he started getting a little bit more sassy,
a little bit, and I didn't like that.
Yeah, because you get frustrated
because you don't have a cigarette
and you're just like, hmm, what am I gonna do now?
You know, okay, let me do some yoga,
okay, let me do some work.
Let's see who's on YouTube, let's say it's on TV,
let's go outside, you know, but if it gets new.
very hard. It's hard. You know, I've smoked probably since I was like, like 14, 13 or 14. And it's been like,
What since you were 14? Yeah.
How did you even get the cigarettes at 14? They just gave it to you?
because I went to my school was like six through 12th grade right and so um and I was friends
with like the older kids and so I that back then cigarettes were like four to five dollars a pack
you know and so I give the guy sometimes you work yeah packs and stuff like that and yeah and I
looked out and he goes smoke on that my parents hated cigarettes they both they both used to be
smokers but they both they both like could talk cold turkey like earlier in their lives and um and
Everything they said don't do, I pretty much did, you know, but then they said, oh, don't they said never get attached to they never want to tattoos and then my mom know my mom has like tattoos on her wrist like she has a cherry
every single time, so I just don't have any.
Maybe that's meant to be,
because it is very, very permanent and it's like,
you know, and it's a pain if you ever do want to get it,
then they're removed and so inexpensive.
So yeah, it's best when it just happens,
it falls into place and stuff like that.
So yeah, I love my new last tattoo that Spunky sponsored
and so I'm satisfied.
Yeah.
How many tattoos do you have do you do do well maybe you don't want to say but
two three four five six six I think I've got my big one on my back yeah and the
ones on my arms and yeah and I
Lot of them I got from from people like that tattoo artist for free like in the houses and stuff like that, but
Yeah, so that I might get a tattoo. I always wanted like some really like well done tattoos of you know
different
You know animals or something on my arm and I would get it on the arm where I am
You know that scooter accident I had like like the skin came back
But you know being that it's you know, I'm always gonna have like a little discoloration. This is where I would get it
So I think if I ever do I'm just gonna get like maybe like
a dragon and like a unicorn or you know mystical stuff all down and then I'll have like a sleeve and
I can be a badass finally. That'd be awesome. Yeah. That's what I would do. Yeah, there you go big lips.
I could put it on the AI, you know, maybe I should like look at what it would look like, like make an AI version of myself and do that.
Maybe I'll do that. I'll do that today. There's a really nice tattoo place close to where I am right now.
and I drove by earlier and I was like,
and now we're talking about tattoos.
Maybe I should, maybe I should go ahead
and get my first tattoo.
Cause I gotta hurry up and do everything
I always wanted to do like before I get too, too, too old.
I'm very conscientious of that at this point.
Well, and you certainly do not you don't you don't look older. I do I look old now. Let's keep it real
I do I know I do and I'm pissed about it
I really honestly, you are gorgeous and it'll be gorgeous.
I think no matter what age you are, but yeah.
Well, I'm gonna get my plastic surgery.
I'm just, I am gonna fight the aging process.
I haven't really, I've kind of gotten started, you know?
The quitting smoking, that's a part of why.
Cause I feel like, okay, gotta hold on to the youth.
So we're doing that.
I do still want to be skinnier, so we're going to work on that.
I am going to go ahead and get a tattoo this year because I've always wanted one, and you
know, so if it's permanent, I'm not going to live forever, or will I?
And so I'm going to do that, and when I'm 50, I'm going to start getting some cosmetic
surgery just because I want it, so I'm going to do it.
So, you know, I'll be, I'll be one of those women. I don't care. But I don't want to look ugly when I'm old, you know, because I see what aging is. And I see it, you know, at first when you're young, you don't really think, oh, I'm so worried about it.
But once you start approaching 50, you think about it.
You do have the Capricorn thing going because like the Capricorn is kind of it sometimes age and reverse and
You know, I think that we both look good for it for age, you know, I don't have any yeah
Well, I mean for our age, but I want to look better. I want to I want to you know, really look amazing
When I'm in my 50s, so I'm gonna do it. You know, I've saved my money
I have you know, I can do it so I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna get a chin and plant
I'm going to get a facelift, you know, I'll see fitness wise, body wise where I'm at
at that point, but yeah, you know, I'm going to I'm going to use the cheat system.
Yeah, well, whatever makes you, you know, feel more confident, you know, it sounds like
you're probably doing it for the right reasons, you know, it's just like, oh, it's all the
wrong reasons.
Pure Vanity. Pure Vanity.
That's okay, that's legitimate.
But it's basically our own confidence
that, you know, I do
think that you're gorgeous. Thank you.
I know everyone does so yeah but I'm gonna thank you for that you know you had a great
live yesterday you went through the codex I just I did a big update on the codex today I think I added
like a thousand more okay more stuff all right I'll take a look I'll take a look well the transcripts
are you know that's really where you can do a lot but I've just been looking through some of your
you know talked about and whatnot um so what's going on with with with tier number two of the code
if you're too well i yeah i need to i need to build it up a little bit i think i mean i mean
because i think i started out with like i had a like a like a lifetime or like a year or lifetime
membership option and so i need to but i need to kind of um
Get more stuff for it because I think there's other there's other really cool features. I can I can add that that
Including like I think like maybe like
Some edit some editing capabilities like the ability to like to manage your your own page and stuff
I'm pretty well put what you want on there or things like that. I think or
um and that's what I was looking at when it came to the description of tier two when it said that
I could create my own packages or my own packs or you know favorites whatever that's what I
wanted to do and that's and I couldn't do and I was like uh but you know I get I get overexcited
about projects but no um I'll figure that out as soon as possible like yeah because I've been able
But thank you for becoming like the first official member, um, you know, the first, uh,
Well, I'm number number three.
Yeah, but I think I might be the first too, but yeah.
Oh, okay. Am I really the first?
Yeah.
I like being number one.
So you got the seniority in the cult in a good way, so.
Yeah, and I was running from the cult.
Now I'm all about the cult.
I might end up being the cult's biggest promoter
that's ever been.
Who knows?
Well, it's a cult for leaders, not for followers.
It's like, so you certainly are a leader.
Well, I want to be a leader. I want to do stuff. I want to, you know, make a few changes in this world
before I'm too old to do so. So I'm running faster than I normally would.
All right. What about, like, are you going to have on-demand merch?
Okay. Yeah. I mean, yes, I would love to do some more merch, like on-demand, like so.
How would like, um, how would that on demand meaning, meaning you wouldn't have to have any of your own stock. It would just be like, let's say somebody wanted a cult of psyche coffee cup.
There's all sorts of, you know, websites to where you can sign up. People can buy the cup. They create the cup. They ship it to the customer or a cult member. And that way it's all hands off for you.
percentage of the profit, but at the same time, you don't have to house any of your own merch.
But you could house your own merch when I think about it, because you're stationary,
but I think you should have merch. Yeah, I would like to do some like cool, like cool,
like remember you had it, you told me like, you know, having really nice, like, like a,
like leather bound or like, you know, like things like that, like really. Yes. Yes.
it's like some higher stuff.
And also, I think I might even do like a haters club line,
like the psyche haters club.
So I can get my trolls in on them.
And I think I might be hated just as much.
But do you really want to put that into the universe?
Well, it's kind of like, it's kind of, well, yeah,
it's kind of funny, but I do like to monetize even the trolls,
you know, it's like, but uh.
Well, you could, you could, you could, or yeah, yeah.
But um.
It's a way.
No, no, they're probably they probably wouldn't wouldn't be big customers, but um, yeah
But I yeah, I do have a like a lot of good
you know the ability to
To do to do some of the art I do and stuff like and it's I think you can make some pretty cool stuff like
I think I did. I do have a fashion merchandising degree. I have my, I have my, I know you do. You told me, yeah, yeah.
So you could make amazing merch when I think about it.
Yeah, so I need to do that and, you know, all the, all the site and then.
Here's an idea. Okay, it just popped to my mind. Okay, if you're going to stream with
Q, there needs to be a purpose. Okay? Yeah. What if you were to get some cult of Psyche's
shirts made up and then he could be the model? Oh, yeah, we can have a fashion show. And uh,
And, you know, fashion shows, I did a few fashion shows,
like, you know, a backstage of some fashion shows.
And people are back, there are some pretty attractive guys
back there, you know, changing, but I don't know.
I hate Q, but I want to help him in some way.
I just hate him.
He makes me sick.
Oh, he makes me sick.
But if I, but if I didn't see certain redeeming things in him, he wouldn't make me as sick as he does.
You know, I've been thinking about that whole, you know, when you do have an extreme aversion to something or a person, it usually does have to do with it being that it's something about yourself.
that you don't wanna face or just something
that you need to contend with.
And I do know what it is about Q,
why, you know, I'll say it public right now.
He really hit a sore spot with me when he said something
that has led me to say to myself, okay,
I need to get real about a goal that I might not achieve
but that I am gonna try to do.
He specifically said that he hopes I'm never a parent because that's the one thing that I want the most
He was correct
That's what really made me really upset mm-hmm, but he's right and
It's funny that he said it when he said it because
I was thinking about that before
and I'd spoken to my doctor about it.
I'm like, you know, if I wanted to, could I?
So, you know, and I did a stream about it
over on my Alexandra Marys channel.
I talked about it a little bit, but I can't.
But am I going to?
So here's what I'm doing with myself.
Quitting the smoking, putting in the real effort,
not this year, next year, I'm gonna go the donor route.
I'll have to be a single parent. It could potentially kill me or at least give me a health issue
Hopefully not because I would be a really really really freaking old mom
But it bothers me that I've never tried
so
Yeah, I
Spoke to my aunt about it
And she doesn't think I should do it
But I think I'm gonna try
so
But I think I'm not going to go the anonymous donor route.
I talked to you a little bit about it, but there is a couple of people in my life that
I would ask, but if not, I'll have to go the anonymous donor route.
But I just want to do it because you know when I just think about
Certain ways that I felt about myself and certain life choices. I think I thought to myself
It's not something I should do. I've had people say that to me, but
It's something I want to do
So if I do I'm leaving the internet
Just saying, yeah, I
Think you'd be a great mom
And uh, I kind of think I would too like in a serious way. I think so
I think that part of the reason that I might have been kind of
Intrusive or invasive in certain people's lives is because I have too much maternal energy and it it hasn't been channeled
properly
so
Yeah
Yeah, but that's why I got really upset with him because he he did read me properly
Yeah, I didn't like it. Yeah, I mean, I think he'll
He'll say like whatever is gonna what do you what do you think will be like, you know, the
the thing that hurts the most sometimes and it's like that's maybe that's his defense mechanism or
Yeah, it's like once yeah, he
It's pretty cruel cruel, but
Um, yeah, I don't, hopefully I don't think he would actually actually mean the things he says.
Did you see that sweet, you know, he meant it. No, he meant it. He meant it.
But I don't think he's evil, not like some people are.
Um, but he meant it. He also tends to repeat what other people say.
who he talks to and I know who he was repeating he never has to say but I do
know so yeah all right I'm boring your chat I'm gonna get going well it was
good talking to you you too you have a wonderful day thank you thank you for
sharing
Hey, love you.
That was my counseling session for the day,
but sometimes you just need to talk.
All right, take care.
Love you.
Bye.
Love you too.
Yeah, yeah.
Are you all right and talkable?
Exactly.
And, uh, here.
Yeah.
I don't know, some people are just so rude in the chat.
I mean, let's see.
So, I'm here, I'm a cat daddy.
Oh, let's see, there's Mr. Rudy.
Hey, how are you, Rudy?
Hey, sweetheart.
Yeah.
Rudy's Rudy's very and oh and my other cat um tux has been back, too
Like he has he's black. He has like a tiny little bit of um thing on his chest. Yeah, this is Rudy. He's a sweetheart
Hi, baby
Hi sweetheart
But yeah, like tux is actually Lola's son and tricks his brother. I love Alexander too and
Yeah, I wish you're all that. You know, I wanted to be happy, you know, I wish you're all the happiness
Yes
The best people are yes
Corner shop who fingered rock and roll is that is that a is that a song request?
You'd like a song request. I do have a I do have a
I'm doing some song requests recently. Let me see. I'll put up my
Banner
You know if you go to mr. Extendo mr. Extendo's chat
That's Joker Joker is now mr. Extendo and he does
Song requests now
You just I guess you type SR. I don't know if that works in my chat. I might have the nightbot going
Let me see. I'm not sure if it works though yet, but yeah, I mean I am I would be happy to
I think $5 saw requests is not unreasonable because I know like I was getting some pushback from
No, whatever I do, whatever I try to do to monetize this people. Oh wait, it's like they think that like, you know
Like, you know
People don't need to make money or anything like that
But you know, especially, um, like I don't know if I do want to show you to everyone like
saw this announcement yesterday which was pretty exciting and I've never gotten
something like this before I'm in the top 5% of it but does that say I said I
had three hundred eight thousand four hundred and seventy nine views this month
wow how did that happen wow hello yo congrats congrats on the
I mean, I don't know how that happened, but...
Oh, because you got me the greatest.
Analysts you are the people you are great. You are great. The greatest panelist of all time
Yeah, I know and I mean, I think I'm gonna make a short from that last but the back until until Gonzo interrupted
You know, we were a great conversation with sweepy about moving out here
So if you that was pretty funny. Yeah, well, I'll try to do a short about it
The Q leave because Q Q like you know, there's um, you know, she had some great ideas about some uh
some some maybe future streams I'd love to I'd love to do IRO with you and I
promise I would keep my hands myself you know dude I can't but that was sick that
show did a little beep you right now right that was crazy well it sounded
like Hebrew hammer I mean it did it was sick
Yeah, that was I mean it looked like say you know what I mean wink wink. Yeah. Yeah, it did look like sick
It looks like it. He looks like it. I think I think the penis was too big to be sick so I've seen his
Okay, he's shown me a couple times. It looks more like a like a like a vagina, but
More like a mr. Pipes. Oh
My god, how about how did you see that last night? Mr. Big Pipes was he was pretty um, he's a weirdo, bro
He he kept like I don't know like
Like sneak this in you in a way. You know what I mean wasn't even sneaky though
He's like he was like outright try to do it and like be trying to be cute about it or something like that
Yeah, exactly like he was like he thought he was being subliminal with it
But like well, he's doing really obvious and like an irritating
I kept telling him I was like as I can't slow your roll mr. Big Pipes. I don't know where he's been
He's like I mean he's he's upgraded a little bit. It looks like it in his place, but
He, he's in the spectrum, right?
Um, I mean, it's like, I, I'm not sure.
I mean, it's like.
Honestly, like I feel like he's a little like like a little retarded to be I like for real for real
You know why I say that?
Like I like let's say you like you're not stupid, right?
You know like you might play along with certain shit, but you're not stupid
Now for example like the little subliminal shit that he was trying to do with you
You caught on but you were just playing with it. You were like, oh, yeah
But then you called him out you were like, I do like what the fuck and I've said enough
I mean, I'm like he he has no self-awareness like
People don't like like all right. It's cool that he could play the guitar, but
And he has no self-awareness that nobody gives a fuck you could play any and every instrument
Nobody cares on panel.
He has no self-awareness.
He's saying and singing really loud when we're just
in the middle of a conversation with other people.
And it's like, OK.
And then I think basically what I think about him
is I think he might be a little.
I don't know. I don't think he's honestly a little retarded like Pharrell like not trying to dig or anything
but like I think he is and
I saw the the the video with him and the other guy's saint. Oh
Yeah, that's a great video. That's a great video
They're fighting over the guitar like a saint grab his guitar or something like that or and he started
Like you could tell the way he is like socially
You could tell he's like
Because in order to fight with saints to sort of fight with saint like you got to tell saint has like some
Fight in him like you know, he's like, you know, he's he's a nice the kind guy
But you can tell if you piss off same like, you know, he's like a he's like a he could be like a pit bull, right?
And it's like so I don't know why he would
start to fight with him.
But yeah, same kind of,
I don't know if it's considered playing dirty,
but he did kind of almost gouge out his eyeballs,
which was just upon us.
Well, because what's his name?
I don't like calling him Mr. Big Pipes.
I'm gonna call him fucking Mustache.
Mustache was, he was basically telling him,
hey, look, I'm good, like,
like stop trying to take the phone away.
I'm using it.
But St. was like, dude, this is my fucking phone.
What the fuck do you mean?
I can't-
It was over a phone.
I thought it was his guitar.
I thought St. had his guitar as a memory,
some of the wrong memory or something like that.
No, so he was playing his guitar,
but he was using St.'s phone to use the lyrics for the guitar.
And St. was like, all right, enough.
Give me my phone back.
And mustache was like, no, dude, I'm using the phone.
Stop.
And he was like, what the fuck do you mean?
I can't have my phone.
And then they started to go off and someone has your phone and it's like, you know
Because it could they could be like, you know, just going through and scrolling through it and stuff like that
So it is like, you know when you give someone your phone like, oh here look at this picture and then take it and all of a sudden
They're like scrolling through your phone. You're like, I hate that. I
That's why when people when I want to show somebody something
I'll just like send it to their message like dude like you don't know what type of photos there are in there, whether they're good or bad like that's none of your business, you know.
I know. Yeah. Yeah, but I do the same as one of those first, like I met, you know, after
Benny, like Benny would play him and stuff. I guess they're both, I guess they're both
around the same area, like in Pennsylvania or something. And yeah. So I met him and he's
just like, he's always really cool to me in his chat. He's like, what's up? He, I mean,
his, his girlfriend magic is also, she's from South Africa, but she does, she reads cards,
which is a which is a way of divination and here she's really good I'm she's
really cool but yeah so um but I've yeah his his channel everybody is
saint 10 is a saint in the number one zero if you click edit on the photo when
you want to show those so they can't they can't see the others yep I know it's
like I hate like you know
Be careful with your phone out these days, you know people of course you got your bank in there
You got personal info. You never know your girlfriend's photos. She sends you you never know, right?
And at the same time too, it's like there's a lot of scary technology out there now that is like
You know take take your info away. Yeah, people can have you know hack phones and I mean nowadays
You have your PayPal your Apple pay
With just two clicks of a button. So it's like everything is right there. Yeah, and
It's also like I saw like this there's like this magician on YouTube and he exposes all these other
magicians
Magic tricks viewers a mask is like the mass magician, right? Yeah, exactly. Just Jen
But yeah, they got that old show
Well, it was kind of it's kind of like it's a YouTube it's a guy on YouTube
But it's like it's like that show where they used to like have that you know on Fox
They had a special where it's like that. Yes revealed. I love that show
Yeah
And, uh, yeah, so the guy does it, but he like, he's like, totally anonymous, but there
was a guy on his service training, OSINT.
Have you heard of OSINT OSINT?
No.
OSINT is basically the ability to like use these public records and everything.
It's to kind of like putting together a puzzle, but it's like, you can figure out people's
kind of identities by going through like, so they went through, they found like an e here.
Here's one email address he had and they go and then they find like another connection
to that email address.
that the guy, he found the guy's PayPal, which the guy was promoting him openly,
and when you send a PayPal, they show the whole person's name anyway, and so it's kind of crazy.
Oh, we have Q, okay, hold on, hold on, there's Hebrew hammers.
Real quick, I wanted to say, uh, Justin looked very beautiful on a wedding date.
He did, hold on, I think I see this as a real Q. It looks like a Hebrew hammers picture,
I don't, I'm not trusting this. Oh, no, here we go. Hello?
That's no that's the same one. That's the same one this cue. I
Can't tell man, I can't tell he likes to fuck around
No, it's me
Well cute you hear you hear what she says we have a some IRL are you down?
What are you talking about well Alexander was just on and she said that oh I did it felt greasy in here for some reason. Oh shut up
I knew something was up. I knew something strange as a foot. Sorry. I still got moose on my hair
Because but she did but she didn't say you know, maybe you'd be like a model for me. Would you like to be a model?
To be honest with you, Psyche, the closest I ever want to be with you is on this panel.
Fine fine just saying I thought he was about to kick you out. I'm surprised. He did it. I might my my finger's gonna
Bomb me he said the n word a bunch of times
Literally just said it and he didn't say anything well man. It's like, you know kind of was like when I first came in here
I said it's me and I'm worried with the hard R
It's kind of like times in a row, like really fast, the other day, which is like, you know.
Oh yeah, well you deserved it sometimes. It's okay. You know, I'm not a drama f-word, so like,
I kind of, whenever I go to sleep and wake up the next day, I don't give a fuck about what
happened on the panel. If they care, if the people care, then that's on them.
Well yeah, I mean, I'm able to...
Let's see. Oh, you're higher? Upstate high? Yeah.
So how's everyone in the chat doing it?
So, yeah, she was saying Victoria J is about to be exposed.
I don't know if anybody knew.
What? Yeah.
Who's gonna expose her?
I don't know, but I guess there's something going on.
Was she gonna expose her being more fucking annoying than she already is or what?
Oh, shit.
Well, I don't know. I mean
I mean, does anybody have any more information about that if anybody if anybody
Know like does anybody know about that?
So you can know by now Alex just talks she doesn't really sure she just talks so
Little what she says is baloney. I
Know you guys are buddy buddies now, right? But you you know that whether you want to admit it or not
Well, I'll disagree with you, but so let me see that I understand that it's more beneficial for you to be buddy
Buddies with her than have you than have her on your ass. So I get it, but you know, I don't have to tell you
Well, I don't it's not about that. It's like a yeah, I don't look it's because we're we have the same birthday which is like
Um, I think we have a Alex mayors can literally fucking like shoot somebody in the face and people around here
We'll forget about it the next day. It's crazy
You know what? I mean like she made all those fucking videos about good time grandmother, and then he's just like
Come run on my panel
Well, hey people are still talking about shit. I did three years ago. What?
Wait, what did you do three years ago?
Bit on chick I pissed on a fucking I pissed on an Arby's outside table thing
Um, I mean it's a bunch of people. I mean it's like and I think there's like
Well, I got into a conf work a confrontation on stream with my aunt
What else
Yeah, I mean, it's like very that's why it's like, I mean, people will do things and it's like, I think people can, can, can, you know, change and stuff.
Like, and also like, you know, some things are like, I think pissing on a table at Arby's is not like necessarily or spitting out.
Oh, no, it was raining outside and it was nighttime.
So it was like, you know, the outside seating areas, it was one of those type of things and I just took a piss on it.
It was fucking pouring down rain anyways.
Washed off in two seconds
Yeah, I mean
like it's like
There's really like that was right after I spit on that shit cuz I went to our no
I think that was a separate time because I went to Arby's
Because I wanted them to call the police on me. I was trying to get the chat to call the police on me. I
Know right really smart guy
But, uh, they never did. They were just talking shit.
And then I just, I took a piss right out in the open.
And then Zaya called the police on stream.
And the police laughed at Zaya on the phone.
I don't know if you remember that, Arthur.
No, I didn't even know this happened.
Yeah, well, this was back when I was in Pittsburgh,
but he called the police and the police literally
laughed at him on the phone, like, when, because he was trying to,
but he was trying to, he was trying to rat on me.
Oh, shit.
I know that some people out there probably remember that.
This was, like, two, three years ago.
Man.
And, Smith, the trick says I'm back,
but his brother showed up, showed back up,
and his brother's been impeding her every night now.
And that's why... What's the brother's name?
His brother's name is Tux, and he's a black cat with...
He has, like, a little spot of white on his chest.
And he's been gone for, like, a year,
and, like, he just showed back up.
And so, you know...
So I think that's what cats are like sometimes, you know, they'll
That's why I that's why I'm not like people are like, why aren't you like out every stream like, you know
Like looking like looking for him. But first of all, that's a very I
Like having gone through having cats run away before it is a very difficult process
And it's like even if you do find the cat it's like, you know, it's like
They just have their own lives, kind of like,
you're like, what are you doing?
And so, but I do believe you've had a cat missing,
the women's were two weeks.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I mean, my dad had a cat when he lived in Glendale
and he was a kid, like when they got a dog,
the cat took off, like, and then the cat came back.
I think he said like several years later
and saw the dog was still there and then he left to get.
And that's what will happen too.
Sometimes they just don't get along
with another animal in the house.
And
you know, but I kind of like, it's different than a dog, you know, if a dog is missing, it's like
definitely, you know, someone's gonna find the dog, right? It's like, but you know, cats can go
To make some money for McDonald's, Paul. Don't criticize me, but if you think I'm...
I'm being psyched. I mean, let's be honest. It was silly of you to compare losing a cat to losing a child.
No, no, no. I don't see it as a person. I don't know anything about it. First of all, she said...
Didn't hear about this yet.
No, okay. No, I didn't say anything like that. Like what happened was I think like someone said something about like a door for something like that
And I don't know anything about it. Here we go. It's getting worse. Oh my god. Why would you say that?
I don't know anything about it. I don't I'm gonna say I don't know anything about it
And so I said don't talk about people's kids and that's all that's all that I said
No, but you said but Kate it's like I lost my kid. It's just the same. Well, no, no, no, no
Okay, so it's like losing a child them like no, I didn't I said the cat ran away and I and then she was she was
I'm saying like she was like she's saying. Oh, I'm a terrible. She's like, oh, so it's a terrible being a terrible
I love my cats, but when my cat got out for like a couple hours
I was not saying like it was it if my kid got out for a couple hours. I call the police
Ow, ow, ow.
Okay, I didn't even say that.
I didn't even make that comparison.
I said, but she, I said, she was talking about my family and my cats, which are like my kids.
And she said, oh, I was talking about her kids. I wasn't. Okay.
And she's like, Oh, well, you know what? I didn't know.
I don't know anything about it. Like I really hadn't watched that much anyway.
So if you're just going to like talk over me and like, and like make these points that are not even true, then you can just go.
I mean, it's like, you're putting out false narratives and I don't appreciate that.
mean jeez I mean no such comparison I said if anyone knows me apology it's
her first right so okay so because I I did shut it down like and I don't agree
with like talking about anybody's kid but at the same time like this she's
saying I'm slandering me and stuff oh hold on one second I have a call one
second
the fracture, not the fall. Every scar speaks in a language that we can't recall. Betrayal
was in chaos, it was coded design. A map of where you trusted, a map of every blind line.
They smiled like allies, moved like knives in the dark, left you bleeding in silence just
to study the mark. But you didn't disappear, you translated the pain, turned humiliation into
Call the gate
begging from a crowd. Loyalty fetches under pressure and need so you study behavior like
a strategist who reads no emotion unchecked no reaction for free every move calculated
every silence a key you don't chase validation you withdraw your demand now they reach for
your presence they don't understand.
Not loud, not rage, but calculated state Unpredictable rhythm, impossible rid
You become the answer they secretly need You don't reveal, you imply
You suggest let them build your power Inside of their chest
Scarsity sharpens the value you hold Distance converts attention to gold
Design what you
It's real
You learn comfort, I learn fight
Strings in the ceiling, cutting loose
Nothing left for me to lose if it breaks
When truth is said, it was already hanging dead
They don't silence you
They make you silence yours
No, this guy
We're having some, I don't know, because we're having some conversations in chat.
Sometimes it's a good job conversation. Oh my god, it looks kind of weird.
That's the cat. The guy's on the cat. How's everyone doing? Let me see. I'll
put the link up again. Yeah, there's Rudy just having a nap. Okay. There's my link.
I'm going to get a little hungry, so maybe I'll put some food in the oven.
Okay, so here we go.
Okay.
Yeah.
Did I fix what?
Oh, fix what?
Fix what on Jamie?
I'm sorry.
Okay, anybody want to come up and have a conversation?
Everyone's welcome. So
Let's see why did why did Ganda have words all over his notes? I don't know. I think they might have been
Shennerchal words, okay
Come on up
Bakelips, that's you know, that's that's gonna be immediate timeout for you
No, oh
Who's Gonzo Gonzo from the Muppets you kind of it is probably your cousin you Muppet, okay
They get the link up, okay
Okay, there we go
There's the link turn my volume
Yeah. Okay. Um, let's see. Um, I'm gonna put some stuff in the oven or my fryer real quick.
My air fryer.
Yeah
Okay, how are you doing good?
And anybody's welcome up right now. So what's up?
And it's been pretty crazy this I don't know
Yeah, you've been going live late, dude, I'm asleep and you've been going live
Yeah, I've been going in the middle of the night sometimes I sometimes sleep during the day
But I got some good sleep this morning. So yeah
I'm up um and uh yeah it's been a interesting interesting week and uh but yeah um yeah it's
funny bro when people want to act like they know all about me but when I know all about them and
I mean, there is like, there is a lot of that, like, um, sometimes, but yeah, and it's like, I, I just,
I, there's so much said on the, on, uh,
people that I always just like,
just based, based on what, like, how my, my own relationship with them and not
on what everybody says because it's like, you know, just from being slant, like slandered or
had a lot of subset about myself.
But, uh,
Yeah, it's, um, so
I
Clips is obsessed with you, bro. He's a creep. He's gay, too, but he's weird, bro
Yeah, big will be a big hit big clips has made some uh
some pretty
It's a very interesting art of me like
I don't ever seen it like oh
And I I got I have forgiven him for this, but um like this is this is an example of
The art he does of me there we go and see like some of that
It's just like trying to slam you like oh look you're dirty you're gross
I know and that should be his own self. Have you seen him? I've seen videos of him. Oh my god
Well, I mean, I do have his picture. I mean, yeah, I do and I
I mean, yeah, that's the thing is like I've been given like a lot of people's
But from them camming up or whatever or just them and so I mean
He looks like the AI he just you just showed me
Yeah, with lipstick he looks like that except with imagine that but with lipstick
Yeah, that's kind of interesting
No, I saw I saw when where he looked kind of like that he was like this he's been like this and he looked kind of like
It's kind of like that the creator Rick and Morty. I don't look ever seen that guy
Yeah, he had one like that where fucking he was zooming in all close on his lips
And he has like a beard and shit dude, but his lips are he has red lipstick on
And he's like all like smooching the camera and shit do like what the hell, bro
I mean a lot of these people bro are really really creepy man, but you know, it's everybody else. That's a weirdo and creep, you know
Right, I mean it's like and you know
things to me said about about everybody but like I said and like and like less there's been like something act like you know something actually
Happen like you know people getting hurt or something like that
Then there's like just a lot of people can just are just talking on the internet and you know, I don't know
It's like
They could say whatever they want, but they're gonna learn bro with me with my shit anyways
They're gonna learn
Well, yeah, I mean it's like yeah, because it's like there's like just the other day on beat is there or she was saying like oh well
You know, she told me last year don't have LD on because of this and that and then she still has LD on and like
And so it's like and then I but I never had a problem having him on and I just just like because I was like well
It doesn't seem like there's like much
They're like I don't understand so I don't understand why these people want to tell me how to run my show or who to have on or oh
Whether I'm trying to do you're doing a good interviews with them or not or what at whatever like
It's just like people don't even want to like acknowledge that I actually I have a show. I'm a streamer
You know and I'm not like
You know have to compete with you, bro
If I'm up like they're like, oh look, there's gonna be another show where people can't open
and so many people that don't come up
have so much to say about like everything.
I've shown literally like thousands and thousands
of hours of like everything, you know?
And it's so like, how can people like,
I want to see, how about they show me their stuff exactly?
And so it's like, you know, people are just so,
so we get to slander other people sometimes.
And like I said, they're just trying to show,
that's what they do, bro.
Shut other people down because they don't want competition competition for views. I'm telling you, bro
That's where like oh, they're like watch him. Don't watch him
Well, yeah, and it's like and then they're so sure I mean it's like they're watching
Oh, and you know what also they do that's what they do on my shit, bro
There will be like four or five groups of people, bro
That'll be streaming it to discord or whatever, bro
So yeah, I'll say like five people watching because they already learned they're like, oh just stream
Oh watch it on discord and they're like probably like fucking like 60 people bro and five different servers, bro
You're on kick too, and I think you have pretty good numbers on kick
I mean, yeah, cuz yeah, cuz I quit YouTube for like a few months, bro, and I went over to kick and
Started growing over there and then just came back, you know, well at the same time. I said fuck it dude might as well
Yeah
Well, I got banned man, I got banned and my old channel used to blow up dude, that's why they're jealous
That's where the oh, no, no, that's why they're so eager because they don't want that
They were so glad when my channel was banned
And they're like, Oh, we don't have to worry about him. Oh, he's gone. You know what I mean? Like they don't want me to gain that traction again, dude
That's part of it. Like it's that's why it's like kind of trying to cancel me and like and like say and
At the same time it's like they
You know, I there's they're still watching they're still watching and I don't I just don't like the people being intimidated right now
By some by certain people, but I actually I just I just got this thing. I've got like
I'm at 300,000 or something views this month or something like that. So it's like it's like I really has a it hasn't really
I don't think it's I don't think it's I don't think it's really hurt me but
But I'm I guess I don't know what this community thing is like this community
I'm supposed to be a part of which is like I'm not really a part I never felt like a part of it
Like everyone has their own show basically become obsesity, bro
That's what happened with VP after I hung out with VP bro. That's when the obsession started with her
Like, you know, everybody covers her and Clipster that Janney dude or whatever
That that all started because of me, bro
They got obsessed with her bro, so they're gonna they're probably gonna start getting obsessed with you now, man
Well, I have been called the male vegan Patriot at someone said I look
Yeah, I mean, it's like
Man and all then bro, they use box bro Bita uses box bro
Well, I mean it's like yeah, and it's like I really yeah, and people are always like oh well
You just he's sitting over there was like, you know, he hit like people are just keep saying I don't have any viewers or anything
I mean, I I don't I don't I don't I don't bought or anything like that
but
decent I do have a decent amount of viewers I and especially just because I've been around for like just a year and stuff and
So I just don't know
Yeah
Samans and shit will say like 200 and shit like that. Fuck. No, dude. Yeah, and it's like I really
Watching that a blank screen, dude. Yeah
And at the same time, it's like not really like, you know, as long as I have like quality quality people
It's like because I've had over on the chat where it's like, you know
Everyone's just been a troll and like and and so it's like I that's that just makes it difficult like sort of the chat and
Better to have a smaller amount of good people
And so I'm not really, I think I'm so obsessed with numbers or anything, it doesn't really
do me good, especially I'm not even monetized.
And the end doesn't end if you're not monetized.
Yeah, and I like, even being not monetized is fine too, because it's like I can actually
do more what I want to do, like I'm not worried about YouTube rules and stuff.
Pin the link.
Okay, easy, I'll pin the link for it, okay, I'll try to pin it.
No, I think that guy, that guy Tony, I think that corn bomb me today and you know
Yeah, and, you know, and I had the metal, the metal people coming yesterday and stuff, you know, it's like, they come from like, they drive from over an hour away sometimes, and they're just like crestfallen, they're like, I mean, I just say, oh, I'm sorry, you know, whatever.
But they're like, they actually like, they have to drive for hours, waste their gas, and they're coming for free things. And so it's like, it's like, really, I feel bad for these people. And they're, I mean, it's like.
doesn't even do anything to me too. Yeah, I felt bad for them. Yeah, it ain't doing
nothing to me. I had people looking coming over looking like, Oh, he likes it. He likes
it. Stop doing it. Yeah, I mean, yeah, I mean, someone's like last night, there was a really
cute guy that came and I was like, you know, I almost asked. Yeah, I don't know. But I
Well, I mean
Well, I think it was like, you know, like I used to be in my chat and then I mean, he's still but he's like
He's you know, I think he has a lot of alts and stuff like that
He's like and he's a big fan of like betas because he's always like leave beta alone and stuff like that
He's like this is enough enough is enough. He sends a picture of mini-man since vagina
Like hundreds of text messages. He just calls over and over and over just like and it's just like disconnects
Never says anything. It's just a waste of time. It's like he has
much energy for me. It's like ridiculous. Um, but yeah,
the gamble hates me so much that he's defending just Jen on a fake profile,
bro. When he hates her, that's how, that's how obsessed these people are, bro.
They'll team up. There's literally people that hate each other, bro.
That will team up against me, bro.
Yeah. Here's as gamble because it's like, I do, well, I do sort of see like the
Like who's connected that I had that I hadn't really seen before
Based on like how they're watching them interact and stuff like that and and sing because there's
There are like, you know, goon squads or whatever, people have their own like, there's a lot of people that will do stuff to people and then they'll just have other people do it, and so their hands are clean, but it's like, I know it's behind some of the stuff, and like, why they're trying to pull up.
Well, I'll get my hands dirty. I don't give a fuck, bro. I'll get my hands dirty, dude.
Hey, oh yeah, just Jen that on that, that on control is super chat or whatever. Yeah, that was me. Do something about it, bro. What are you going to do about it, Jen? Do something about it.
And and they're saying oh look you're doing this in that don't don't be putting lies on somebody
She's literally over here saying that I raped somebody bro or great
Great vegan patriot bro for you then you saying all this in that hey, bro. That's on you bro. Don't don't act innocent
Don't lie about somebody that could get somebody killed bro, and then act innocent
Yeah, some of these yes some of this stuff like you know cuz everyone's like oh go just go look at like what?
And I I mean I did and it's like I didn't
I don't I just I just like I just see I see something different than what people are saying
What's up, dude, how are you this is easy
Hey shit, baby
Yeah, Jen just other people with your name, bro that have all your fucking. I'm not even
I'm not even gonna go here, bro
Yeah, well, it's like, you know, I think I think anybody has, you know
It's like stuff that people can say stuff about I think I think there's very selective outrage based on different different reasons and
You know, it's just it's just like I'm shit about salmon today, bro
I heard some shit about him. Oh, yeah. I heard some crazy shit about him today, bro
Crazy crazy
Yeah, I don't know and I heard I heard Victoria is is uh
Alexander said if your tour is about to be talks to her and I'm
It's so easy to tell that her voice is a voice changer, bro. Like go literally go look up. What a girl
Okay, dude, well because yeah, well, I mean I could tell that it wasn't I mean this picture of like
I mean it looks like some kind of like like Hollywood actress or something in her photo
But I think she was trying to like take heat off of her by like throwing my name into things and stuff
And so I mean yeah
Well, she was
Just trying to I think she was just taking heat off of herself by bringing up like the situation over situations over here
and stuff like that and I
Don't I don't know. I mean, I she's been on my show and she's been fine on my show, but I
Don't I don't know I don't know why
You know, there's another person without without a photo or without a in their camera on and it's like so
You don't know really you know, who knows what's up? And I don't it's the internet people can be on all
It'll give me a man balls. And so yeah
Yeah, so what is this?
People said where am I doxing? Where am I? I'm not am I doxing anybody on your stream? No
Where am I doxing anyone
So what is it? Yeah, I don't I don't understand what they mean. Yeah, that's all he does. Oh
Why are you letting this dude do this? That's how he is, bro
Right
He's I get accused of doxing, you know, and I've never doxed anybody because I consider doxing would be like, you know
releasing their
address
Her phone number or something like that
Yeah, I've shown pictures
Yeah, so yeah
Do that shit. I don't know if you realize but people will type shit in the chat
Just hoping that thinking that oh if somebody comes and read it, they're gonna see that and think oh look
Because you know people turn on a stream and they look at the chat to see what's going on
So you just type dumb shit, you know what I mean?
Yeah, and I can tell it's the same person coming back over
and over again, like this person.
I mean, I'll do things like if somebody is like being
targeted in the chat, like I will sometimes mod people
based on that.
So it's like they just create kids will just have like people.
I don't know, but I'm trying to get better with mods.
It's hard to deal with mods.
And let's see.
Well, yeah, I don't know.
But yeah, there's a lot of accusations made and how can I sit here and verify anything in your chat?
That's a lie, bro. You know, you could click on my thing on YouTube, right?
Yeah, YouTube and look at everything I posted, right? Yeah, I can see the chat history and
I never never doctor ever, bro in your chat.
No, I don't think so. And so, um, yeah, they lied to lie right to your face, bro. Like they think
this has been my life bro people are literally insane bro they literally know my mom and
like oh you know your son was just arrested for uh um uh doing something to some kid
and you need to pick him up from jail like that's stupid bro like wouldn't when they
see that that it's not true like what do you like what do you think it's gonna do bro
Like why so much is going to become true or something right?
Well, and that sometimes that unfortunately like when people like the lives holding up like a lot of people do believe
Oh shit, and there are a lot of like followers
Out there too and but a lot of the stuff is like the same few people like on several they're called like sock puppet account
They're like, oh, yeah
They're like they come back and forth and it's like people I've never seen before in the chat
And then it's like but they say the exact same thing and it's like
so it's like it makes it seem like it's more of something than it yeah it's all the same people
because why would they need an alt that's just oh brandon's tits or some shit you know what i mean
i know like i don't i'd be like a regular regular um
they're fucking regular name yeah that's crazy that's great i mean um but i will always like i
like i'm but even but i would even talk to i would talk to anybody because it's like i think
Especially if people are having things said about them, like they should not be completely
silent.
I think people should defend themselves, especially if there's not criminal charges or like, you
know, a conviction.
There's, isn't there like, you know, innocent before proving guilty, isn't there?
You know, and even like then it's like.
Even people that have been in prison
For things it's like a lot of people change you know change in prison and things like that. And so
I do believe in like redemption forgiveness. I believe in second chances
Or you know, or I've been given second chances sometimes
I mean many more and so I tried to but yeah, I'm not
I'm not really part of a community. I have my own show and it's like you know whether people want to be here or not
It's like up to them, but it's like I don't I don't know there's a lot of all this hate-watching and
You know accusations and really the worst things being said about people like being thrown around and stuff. So I
Don't know I mean it is crazy
Funny they'll do that some ex porn stars obsessed with me, bro
Like wouldn't you think she would have a better life, you know what I mean?
Well, I mean, I just I don't know much about it, but I'm
And never and you know, I'll pull up a random stream rolling it's her I
Well, I've already had access to everything
I've already looked at everything that she says on YouTube duty. Oh, she does this talk about me
It's like she wants me to go. It's like she wants my attention. That's what I think it is
You know, yeah, cool when girls act like that or whatever boys act like that
That's basically what I think it is man
Yeah, like well, you know, like Bita has like a complete like lives about me like, you know
like six hour or six hour lives where I'm just a topic and like there's pan the whole panel and the whole chat is like
it just hates me and stuff like that and
And it's like it's great
And then she's like that if I like, you know play an old clip of her or something like that
She's some people don't want to
The true past they're being brought up for something like that or I don't want the true then when you do that
Then they'll be like oh look you're obsessed. You're obsessed
They do reverse psychology to try to get you to stop dude. Yeah, it's going to be like oh
And then they come on an alt so it doesn't so they don't look like a hypocrite when they say it
Yeah, and uh, yeah, and so
I don't know, I've also, also her mods, like her mods will be like, you say, I say anything to them, leave them alone, leave them alone.
I never get, I never get dependent anymore. I'm used to not being dependent, so I can defend myself.
And, you know, I guess we learn how to handle it.
And it's like, sometimes it's like, you know, it sometimes is better not to...
I mean, it's like I'd rather not have some of these people in my chat, right?
And it's like and so if they they're gonna boycott me or whatever their audience boycotting me. I really don't care
Yeah
And I don't mind controversy, it's like because that's part of having a show, it's like, you know, it's like, but I like to address it, I don't like to say, oh, or just like anybody else, like speaker defend themselves, that is like considered slander, I think.
Yeah.
Big exaggeration, double standards, like all these people are doing the same or like that.
They're doing worse than me bro, they're doing worse than me bro, but I'm demonized.
It's all off the jealousy basically.
I don't want their audience, that's the thing, I don't want their audience, I want my own.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
I'm glad actually I got rid of all the IT2 people who stopped watching me bro, I'm glad.
And they just come around like once in a while, like hey ma'am, we miss you, please start doing IRL again.
Oh my god, fuck that.
I like to help people. I mean, it's like, I always would have a policy of like, you know, everyone sharing their channels and like, you know,
sometimes I send people to people's chats and stuff like that, and it's just like, I'm so surprised that it's like, not even like...
I mean, it's like, not only they won't promote me at all, they will just like fucking tell
people not to, and then they'll harass shatters and harass, harass donators and stuff like
that.
It's crazy.
And they don't like it when they send it to them.
And so it's like, you know, sometimes-
And they can't say anything, then they block you
or they won't let you say shit.
It's like power.
Right, right, exactly.
And then it's like, and when then you don't have a voice,
then it's like-
And then if they say they don't even make sense,
they're all treat them like Cyrax, treat them like Cyrax.
If they're treating you like Cyrax,
then they would be promoting you.
Yeah, they don't just oh don't oh don't just ignore them over there just ignore them. They don't they don't do that as sirex
Right, and it's like and then even like I said I would have a sirex on the show even though it's a
despicable kind of character like because I think I think he's at the same time
It could be just interesting to talk to a person like that. I do all kinds of people
interesting and you know
or funny or something, there's like, I don't know, there's, there could be, yeah, I know
the PDF stuff is like, I think it's like nowadays, it's, it's like now, I mean, it used to have
to do with children. Now it's like, you know, I get called that because of Benny and Benny's 24
years old. I mean, it's like, and it's like, it's just like, it's, it's kind of like, okay, well,
it's like, you're actually kind of like hurting like the real
like the real cases of it.
Yeah, like what the fuck?
You start telling everybody.
Like that's insane, yeah.
And they were trying to lie saying I was,
I was dating a 24 year old
and they were trying to lie saying
that she was underaged and she was 24.
Right.
I was 24 years ago.
I mean, it's like.
I know it's still it's like there's I just see a big difference between that and like actual
What like what it really is which is like, you know horrible, but
It's just like so over exaggerated it kind of weakens all the cases, you know
What's that I see Alex is coming back on your show. Oh, yeah, yeah
She was oh, yeah, um, we yeah, we had like a we had like a little
a little a little conflict but it's like yeah um yeah we I mean but I uh we
had the same birthday you know and uh actually better I noticed earlier I
noticed I was banning now I'm unbanning so that's good yeah I was um I've
actually I met her I met her in person actually I don't know if you know that
but yeah
And so she's actually the only person I've met in person like of everybody. I'm surprised I haven't met more people in person
but I'd like to do
some IRL streams of people, but
It's just it's kind of hard for me to travel around so
Well, I mean it's like
I don't know what bakelips is talking about. Okay. Yeah, so I don't know
Yeah, I mean
Saying that I sexually assaulted VP then show it where
Well, I saw the I just in the aftermath. He was like kind of like laughing about it
Yeah
Bro, they sent her all kinds of money. She got all she it worked out better than it's I want to have it bro for both of us
Right, I mean
Um, I think to say, you know, S.A. is something that's really, really harsh, um, harsh kind
of claim to make on somebody and, you know, I mean, it's like, so
Especially coming from people that had sex with dogs, bro, like, that's sick, dude.
I'm not going to say their name on here, bro, but somebody that's lying about me and slandering
me, bro.
I have proof, bro.
Bro, they confess, dude, to doing stuff with dogs, but then they turn around and say that,
Don't fuck out of here, dude.
Well, yeah, thank you for not saying it.
Thank you for not saying names.
I appreciate it.
Yeah, it's a real like, like, like I got them.
I'm going to show that tonight, too, bro.
It's like, I got the proof, bro.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, and people say I eat my cats.
I mean, I mean, it's like, it's in a serious way, you know?
And it's like, these things are just like so.
So ridiculous this person who said I said it was them who said I said it was them
guilty conscience
People reveal themselves bro, just like you said in that AI song, bro
People reveal themselves, bro. Yeah, and it's like and yeah, and that's the good thing
So that's why I do like, you know, like I do like when people like what are able to
To do that and it's like and then not like, you know, yeah me saying things and you know, it's like, you know, yeah, exactly
Cuz uh, I really don't I really don't know and I say and I don't have time to go through
Yeah, I'm not trying to convince you of anything. I'm just kind of you know
You know, I don't have no intention of turning any you against anyone. I don't give a fuck, bro. You know what I mean?
right
Because I yeah, because it's like you know as long as people are I am to them and there's been people that have been just been so
So so horrible to me like and said the worst things and it's like I mean
I've even like forgiven some of most of these people right, but it's like
But and I don't know I treat my I treat others like I kind of want to be treated and I would not want to be
slander silence than not given a given a voice and especially if it's like
You know, I just don't have how big followers people are can be sometimes and and I try to hello
Yeah for the bike no that person. Oh, I'm sorry. I'll be right back
They first thing is
Yeah, okay, thank you for that. Thank you. Sorry about that. It's okay. Do you want his number?
No, he's his fake numbers, so it doesn't help. Thank you so much. You can report the ad though. Thank you. I appreciate that
Okay, thank you. Thank you. Yeah, just yeah, so you can see
But he's literally sitting there texting like wasting the people's time. It's like
Hey, bro, put a sign, dude, the sign law.
Yeah, it's doing nothing to you, bro. You get used to it. Like maybe at first it's kind of like
Unsettling, bro
Yeah, bro. I'm telling you after a certain point. You don't give a fuck dude. It does nothing dude. I feel worse for these
Bro, even the cops calling me
None of it bothers me bro. Nothing dude. Like I'm so desensitized, bro
Right and the police know me now like it's actually this is so they know everything that's going on with it and stuff
And so their police are actually really nice and sympathetic give really good advice. Yeah
Yeah, I'm gonna take my hand now, bro. Well, they don't even come now. They don't know they don't even be it don't even come now
Bro, but yeah, last few times they can they just shake my hand, bro
And they say that they hate the motherfuckers that are doing it, bro. Yeah
They said that they said all they're doing is making us like you and then putting a target on their back,
bro. That's what the cops said, dude.
Yeah. And fortunately, some of these people are out of state, makes it hard or like, you know,
even in different countries and stuff like that. But yeah, as for a bit, yeah, no, pizza, like the
pizzas were like one thing. It's like, um, but yeah, I've been getting the scrap metal people,
they put ads for free bikes and stuff like that. And then it's like, they only put the address,
they'll just get the person to call.
and then they'll direct the person and so it's like it's really hard to you know just different phone numbers and stuff and so it's I mean it's just basically a little bit of an annoyance especially if I'm like you know sleeping actually the worst thing is like sending people to like turn off the gas or the water and stuff like that and like and then they come and then so they actually will call the police when when that happens like that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's
because they say that a lot of those places like they're gonna charge you like $150 just for coming out
right exactly yeah and it's like well thankfully i haven't you know no one's giving me a bill but
i mean it's like no they can't no fuck no they can't dude yeah i don't know it's like uh
I think that, but that's what's good about, like, you know, being able to actually track
people down, because you can actually can start to get restraining orders, things like that.
And, and so I will, you know, you know, now that I, yeah, it's just good that I, I do
have allies, allies that can help me out.
I got your back, bro.
Thank you.
I'm a smart motherfucker, dude.
I got your back, bro.
Because, yeah, without that, it's like, you know, people can just feel free to do this.
But the thing is, like, nobody really cares.
Like, you know, people actually thought, like, we're, like, laughing about it.
Like, most people think it's, like, funny or whatever.
It's like, well, how would they like that if it was them?
Or it was, like, their family or anything like that?
It's, like, it's just really, like, bad karma and bad juju.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
So you're doing this at it, I know.
Yeah, I just hope that I mean I really do feel like people will get their karma and it's like and
Basically, it's not gonna be good, right? Yeah. Yeah, and oh, yeah, someone's come over. We're looking for spoons, too
They're like
Spoons like you literally like looking over from free spoons. He's crazy
Oh my God. Yeah. I mean, it's like free. Yeah. Yeah. And a free bikes. I mean, it's
like, yeah, who wouldn't come for like a free bike? But it's like lawnmower. Let me have
a lawn outside. I would have a lawnmower to give away.
All right, bro. I gotta take a shower, bro. I've had a long day.
Oh, thank you. Thanks for a good night, Chad. And have a good day. Okay.
Well, yeah, anyone's welcome up anyone's anyone's welcome up and you know, I don't I don't I want to get over a chance
Sounds good
Take care, bro, too. Oh
Lola's here. I'm cuddling with me. Oh
It's Lola
She's a very cuddly cap
Yeah, so everyone check out my the codex though
I mean, I did put like a lot of new stuff on it. I'm updating it. I'll put my I'll put it in the chat
This is this is every all my episodes are archived
Um, you know, I have the transcripts are all scraped and then these are analyzed every topic
This has been discussed everybody that's been on the show. Oh, yeah, they're sorry for the wrong wrong
Just cold.me. I wish I had that that URL one is cold codex.me and
I
Think even if you're big pipes who is like, you know
Kind of like really trying to be harsh last night. Even he was like, okay, it looks pretty good
Hey, babe, but I think I think I do have like half a million transcripts
transcript segments on there like everything on the show you can I mean you can I've been almost on almost every day
for like the past over a year and so
Yeah, let's see running from Dahmer apartment, let me see
Take photos Dahmer well actually, but I started out in the beef sector and the in the
Mode three sector or whatever and they would call me Dahmer
Because I was like the only I was a white person. They thought I was kind of weird
But I don't know. Maybe I didn't have the glasses and stuff too
It's not not like he's like the worst-looking person, but yeah, it's like not like he's like, but do I really care?
No, my actual last my real last name is like, you know
I'll dox myself. It's Bates. And so, you know, I've heard the psycho jokes my entire life
Master Bates, I've heard all this stuff all my life. And so it's not really
anything
anything that different, right? But um
Who are the streamers in that community? Uh, I don't know. I'm not sure what you're referring to. Um, but um
Yeah, so
Yeah, but and also the music I've been making I don't know some people like a lot of people like to say whatever
because I do utilize not only AI my music but and
Like a lot of things like you know, they
Right now you don't need to really know how to code anymore. Like I was able to do the website without any outside
Any outside people because now that you know, you carry able there's the ability to code and stuff and
It's basically like a calculator and it's like so it's like people being mad at somebody for using a calculator for an account and using a calculator
It's like does it mean they're bad at math? No, does it I mean it is it?
like isn't technology, but I thought it's therefore to do to make things easier for us or to like, you know
Give us the ability. Like, you know, I don't have a recording studio
I don't have like, you know, a hundred people to do like sound engineers and and you know
Different people playing different instruments and and all this stuff and I can't I'm not a great singer
I mean, I'm an okay singer, but I'm not like, you know
anything or it's like, oh, so I don't know I think
I'm able to it's like if you have if you have talent it can it can amplify the talent
I'll say that right and it's like and so and I think it's pretty clear that I do have some
kind of talent somewhere and maybe you guys can you'll figure it out along the way but
uh and it's like it's not like I just have like the stuff printing itself out and uh
Making itself. It's like, you know, I do have to what streamers that I miss other good pussy good pussy show
If you know good pussy
She's and you know, there's different. They used to go in the show called China
And she would do this hood jeopardy and I would I mean I would always lose but
But it was pretty good. Yeah
Yeah, and that's that's why artists have music and it's yeah exactly and it's like and also I think there's like
I think so much of like the real recording industry like people think oh well
There's these are real like you think Britney Spears is really that talented like I mean
It's like do you think she's like sitting there writing her music and doing that and and creating the music or anything or she's sitting there
You know goes into a studio like chewing gum and like you know
They kind of like warbles on the mic for a few minutes, and then they fucking make albums out of it, right?
link them. I think it's good pussy and she has dollar signs for the S's. I mean I can try to find her.
But the thing about the beef sector is like it's really hard to talk because I'm not I'm not trying
to like be like stereotypical or anything and talk about doxing and like that is like they're
barely bad with doxing there and like all that kind of stuff but it's like it's basically if you're
is like over there and it's like everyone's kind of like like a lot of people are like him
where it's like he they just like talk and I've literally sat up there for an hour and not been
they just have one person screaming the whole time I can I can lean good pussy let me see
I think it's like the good pussy show and her name is um
I don't know if we'll find it, we'll check it out real quick.
But actually, but it is like, it was a good place to like learn.
Like to get, before, okay.
So it's like, when I came into this community,
it wasn't, or in this area of YouTube,
or these YouTube streets or whatever,
it was nothing like really surprised me too much.
I mean, they do doxing at the 90 day fiance community.
I mean, it's like, and it's like really serious.
Strange doxing where it's like there's like, you know, they have these Facebook groups
secret Facebook groups where they're like, you know giving
Like the people's kids schools and stuff like that and that's for like the 90s Beyonce
I mean, it's like how how I mean how serious can they I don't understand why people would do that and that's pretty sick
so that people would
Do that kind of shit. It's it's pretty crazy, but um, let me see I might might end like a little early
and
Oh my gosh
Yeah, I might end a little early out because I will be back tonight.
I got some stuff to do, but I want to thank all the guests today.
Thank Alexandra and Arthur and Brandon and everyone that came up.
I appreciate everyone in the chat, all the mods.
People thank you for participating.
I hope.
Everyone is having a good day, and we'll have a great day, and I'll be back tonight
and you guys
Have a happy happy Wednesday. Okay, and I'll just play us out with some the song. Okay. I'll talk to you soon. Okay. Thank you
i'm sinking through the floor again the walls are breathing wrong
the door won't stay what door should stay the light is all too long
i'm running from the thing i was the mirror shows a stranger
the ground keeps giving way beneath but wait there's a hand
Even in the nightmare I'm not alone
Even when the darkness swallows whole
There are helpers here who know the shape
Of every trap that fear can make
They can wake me when I'm trapped
They can show me where the seams are
They can turn the tarot into gold
Sweet dreams from the-
architecture walls that shift and slide
I'm drowning in a room with no way out, nowhere
Is it just inside?
The fear becomes so solid, it feels like the only truth
And I forget that nothing here is real
And I'm a light, a voice
Even in the nightmare, I'm not alone
takes control there are helpers here who see the way through every maze that night can make
they can pull me through the veil they can break the spell i'm under they can turn the suite
into the light turn the dark into the bright
to believe that I'm stuck here in the loop that the horror is the only truth that
there's nothing left to hold but the helpers know a secret every nightmare has
a seam every terror is a door and I can't wake they know the words to whisper they
know
They can show me what is real
They can turn the sweet nightmares into honey
Turn the fear into a meal
The helpers are here
The helpers are real
The helpers know how
Into dust